export const quiz = [
  {
    question: "1 + 1 = ",
    A1: 1,
    A2: 2,
    A3: 3,
    A4: 5,
    answer: "A2"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 2 = ",
    A1: 1,
    A2: 2,
    A3: 3,
    A4: 5,
    answer: "A3"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 4 = ",
    A1: 1,
    A2: 2,
    A3: 3,
    A4: 5,
    answer: "A4"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 1 = ",
    A1: 3,
    A2: 5,
    A3: 7,
    A4: 11,
    answer: "A1"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 3 = ",
    A1: 3,
    A2: 5,
    A3: 7,
    A4: 11,
    answer: "A2"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 5 = ",
    A1: 3,
    A2: 5,
    A3: 7,
    A4: 11,
    answer: "A3"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 9 = ",
    A1: 3,
    A2: 5,
    A3: 7,
    A4: 11,
    answer: "A4"
  },
  {
    question: "3 + 5 = ",
    A1: 8,
    A2: 13,
    A3: 124,
    A4: 16,
    answer: "A1"
  },
  {
    question: "8 + 5 = ",
    A1: 8,
    A2: 13,
    A3: 124,
    A4: 16,
    answer: "A2"
  },
  {
    question: "8 + 8 = ",
    A1: 8,
    A2: 13,
    A3: 124,
    A4: 16,
    answer: "A4"
  }
];
